<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teams on Meta-Research Innovation Center Berlin</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teams on Meta-Research Innovation Center Berlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>John Ioannidis</title>
      <link>/team/johnioannidis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/johnioannidis/</guid>
      <description>John P.A. Ioannidis, MD, DSc is the C.F. Rehnborg Professor in Disease Prevention, and Professor of Medicine, of Health Research and Policy, of Biomedical Data Science, and of Statistics at Stanford University and an Einstein BIH Visiting Fellow at Charité – Universitätsmedizin Berlin. Dr. Ioannidis is internationally recognized as a leader in empirical studies assessing biases, replication, and reliability of research findings in biomedicine and beyond. He has received numerous awards and honorary doctorates and titles and he is a member of the US National Academy of Medicine and of the European Academy of Sciences and Arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Hardwicke</title>
      <link>/team/tomhardwicke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/tomhardwicke/</guid>
      <description>Dr Tom Hardwicke completed a BSc in Psychology at Cardiff University, MRes in Brain Imaging and Cognitive Neuroscience at The University of Birmingham, and PhD in Experimental Psychology at University College London before joining the Meta-Research Innovation Center at Stanford (METRICS) as a Postdoctoral Fellow in 2017. After two happy years in the Californian sunshine, Tom is now heading across the pond to Germany in January 2019 to set up the Meta-Research Innovation Center Berlin (METRIC-Berlin).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>