<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teams on Meta-Research Innovation Center Berlin</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teams on Meta-Research Innovation Center Berlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> John Ioannidis</title>
      <link>/team/johnioannidis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/johnioannidis/</guid>
      <description>John P.A. Ioannidis, MD, DSc is the C.F. Rehnborg Professor in Disease Prevention, and Professor of Medicine, of Health Research and Policy, of Biomedical Data Science, and of Statistics at Stanford University and a BIH Visiting Fellow funded by the Stiftung Charité and the Einstein Foundation Berlin. Dr. Ioannidis is internationally recognized as a leader in empirical studies assessing biases, replication, and reliability of research findings in biomedicine and beyond. He has received numerous awards and honorary doctorates and titles and he is a member of the US National Academy of Medicine and of the European Academy of Sciences and Arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tom Hardwicke</title>
      <link>/team/tomhardwicke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/tomhardwicke/</guid>
      <description>Dr Tom Hardwicke completed a BSc in Psychology at Cardiff University, MRes in Brain Imaging and Cognitive Neuroscience at The University of Birmingham, and PhD in Experimental Psychology at University College London before joining the Meta-Research Innovation Center at Stanford (METRICS) as a Postdoctoral Fellow in 2017. In 2019 Tom moved to Berlin to help set up the Meta-Research Innovation Center Berlin (METRIC-B). He has now moved to the Department of Psychology at the University of Amsterdam, but continues to collaborate with QUEST and METRIC-B as a Visting Fellow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sophia Crüwell</title>
      <link>/team/sophiacruwell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/sophiacruwell/</guid>
      <description>Sophia Crüwell completed a BA in Natural Sciences (Part II) and Philosophy (Part I) at the University of Cambridge, and an MSc (Research) at the University of Amsterdam, where she majored in Psychological Methods and Statistics and minored in Logic. She has just started her PhD in Metascience with METRIC-Berlin and plans to focus on researching incentive structures. You can also find her co-hosting the Open Science focussed podcast ReproducibiliTea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>